const triviaQuestions = [
  {
    question: "1. Who won the 2023 wimbledon men's/women's final?",
    choiceA: "Jimmy Neutron/Cindy Vortex",
    choiceB: "Danny Phantom/Samantha Manson",
    choiceC: "Carlos Alcaraz/Markéta Vondroušová",
    choiceD: "Spongebob Squarepants/Sandy Cheeks",
    answer: "Carlos Alcaraz/Markéta Vondroušová",
  },
  {
    question: "2. What color are Goomboss's pants in paper mario 64?",
    choiceA: "Pizza with extra cheese",
    choiceB: "Salad",
    choiceC: "Red and white",
    choiceD: "RTX 4090",
    answer: "Red and white",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3. What is the term used to describe the penalty of ejection from a soccer match?",
    choiceA: "Red Hot",
    choiceB: "Red Card",
    choiceC: "Red Robin",
    choiceD: "Red Sox",
    answer: "Red Card",
  },
  {
    question:
      "4. What band had the hit song 'Round and Round' as their biggest hit single in 1984?",
    choiceA: "Mouse",
    choiceB: "Ratt",
    choiceC: "Mickey",
    choiceD: "Minnie",
    answer: "Ratt",
  },
  {
    question: "5. Where is the historic sanctuary Machu Picchu located?",
    choiceA: "Bikini Bottom",
    choiceB: "Saturn",
    choiceC: "Mushroom Kingdom",
    choiceD: "Peru",
    answer: "Peru",
  },
  {
    question: "6. What has keys but can't open locks?",
    choiceA: "A very bad nightman",
    choiceB: "Michael Myers",
    choiceC: "A piano",
    choiceD: "Luigi",
    answer: "A piano",
  },
  {
    question:
      "7. What do you call the process of putting new strings on a guitar?",
    choiceA: "Scooping",
    choiceB: "Stretching",
    choiceC: "Jumping",
    choiceD: "Stringing",
    answer: "Stringing",
  },
  {
    question:
      "8. True/False - It is illegal to push a live moose out of an airplane in Alaska.",
    choiceA: "True",
    choiceB: "Why would you even do that",
    choiceC: "Like who thinks of this",
    choiceD: "Wild, I know",
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "9. What was the Spice Girls' debut album called (1996)?",
    choiceA: "Sugar",
    choiceB: "Spice",
    choiceC: "Everything nice",
    choiceD: "Chemical X",
    answer: "Spice",
  },
  {
    question: "10. Which country has competed at every FIFA World Cup event?",
    choiceA: "Brazil",
    choiceB: "Broheim",
    choiceC: "Broski",
    choiceD: "Broseidon",
    answer: "Brazil",
  },
  {
    question: "11. What is the rarest blood type in humans?",
    choiceA: "F-",
    choiceB: "C++",
    choiceC: "Z-",
    choiceD: "AB+",
    answer: "AB+",
  },
  {
    question: "12. Which of these is a commonly used side dish in cooking?",
    choiceA: "Taters",
    choiceB: "What's taters precious?",
    choiceC: "Po-tay-toes",
    choiceD: "Boil em, mash em, stick em in a stew",
    answer: "",
  },

  {
    question:
      "13. What is the name of the most well-known enemy mob in Minecraft?",
    choiceA: "Creeper",
    choiceB: "Aw man",
    choiceC: "So we back in the mine",
    choiceD: "Got our pickaxe swingin from side to side",
    answer: "Creeper",
  },
  {
    question: "14. What is considered the most controversial ice cream flavor?",
    choiceA: "Anakin Skywalker",
    choiceB: "1TB nvme ssd",
    choiceC: "Mint Chocolate Chip",
    choiceD: "Stratocaster",
    answer: "Mint Chocolate Chip",
  },
  {
    question:
      "15. Equal to roughly 746 watts, what animal-based unit is used to measure the rate at which work is done?",
    choiceA: "Donkeystrength",
    choiceB: "Llamathrust",
    choiceC: "Horsepower",
    choiceD: "Zebraforce",
    answer: "Horsepower",
  },
  {
    question:
      "16. What is the name of the effect that distorts a guitar's sound?",
    choiceA: "Dehydration",
    choiceB: "Distortion",
    choiceC: "Prescription",
    choiceD: "Education",
    answer: "Distortion",
  },
  {
    question:
      "17. Fill in the blank. The Statue of Liberty was a gift from _______.",
    choiceA: "Frankenstein",
    choiceB: "France",
    choiceC: "Princess Peach",
    choiceD: "Ugandan Knuckles",
    answer: "France",
  },
  {
    question: "18. What is the noise a robot makes?",
    choiceA: "Beep bop",
    choiceB: "the meep mop",
    choiceC: "the floor",
    choiceD: "whoosh",
    answer: "Beep bop",
  },
  {
    question: "19. Which of the following is a computer part?",
    choiceA: "Bowser",
    choiceB: "Redstone Lamp",
    choiceC: "CPU",
    choiceD: "Morgott, the Omen King",
    answer: "CPU",
  },
  {
    question: "20. Fill in the blank. 'It's not just a boulder! ______'",
    choiceA: "THIS IS SPARTA!",
    choiceB: "*Through happy tears* It's a rock",
    choiceC: "You're killing me, Smalls.",
    choiceD: "So you're telling me there's a chance?",
    answer: "*Through happy tears* It's a rock",
  },
];

export default triviaQuestions;
